Beverly Cassara Papers
Beverly Cassara Papers
- Correspondence-subject files
  - Doerry, Gerd, 1976; 1978,; 1982-1984,; 1986-1987,; 1991,; 1992,; 1995,; 1997; correspondence, paper "The preservice training of adult educators in the universities of the Federal Republic of Germany" (Box 7)
    See also Audiovisual material: German adult educators interviews: Doerry.
  - Dohmen, Gunther, 1985-1986; undated; clipping, paper co-authored with William Rivera "Political system, education policy and lifelong learning," manuscript of AAACE presentation "The end of the wall: Adult education on trial" (Box 7)
  - Dolff, Helmuth, 1975; 1980,; 1982; head of the Deutscher Volkshochschul-Verband (German Adult Education Association); correspondence, photos (Box 7)
    See also Audiovisual material: German adult educators interviews: Dolff.
  - Draper, James, 1990; 1991; correspondence, paper co-written with BC, "International Studies in Adult Education" (Box 7)
  - Düchting, Helga and Werner, 1982-1984; 1986,; 1989-1998 (Box 7)
    See also Audiovisual material: German adult educators interviews: Düchting.
  - "Eat Swiss" (BC article), 1964 (Box 7)
  - Educational Opportunity Center, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Efrati, A—, 1967; letter from Israel concerning the Six-Day War (Box 7)
  - Ellis, David L., 1993 (Box 9)
    See also Distance education.
  - Engels, Elmar, 1976; 1978,; undated (Box 9)
  - ERIC, 1968; 1975,; 1990-1996 (Box 9)
    See also Writings: Miscellaneous: Microfiche of papers in ERIC.
  - "Europe by Tent" (BC article), 1964 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax County Adult Education Program, 1971; BC gave workshop, "Seminar for Mature Women" (Box 9)
  - "Falkenstein conference, June 1986" [supplied title], BC presented; conference program and papers, BC notes and souvenirs (Box 9)
  - Federal City College (FCC), See University of the District of Columbia.
  - Federal Women's Program, 1975; 1978; correspondence, photos (Box 9)
  - Folk Education Association of America, 1990-1993; correspondence from Christopher Spicer and others, newsletters, copy of Spicer's paper "Folk Education: Resurrecting Roots of Adult and Experiential Learning Theory" (Box 9)
  - Follett Publishing, 1982; correspondence, review of book by Sallie Westwood (Box 9)
  - Former students (Box 9)
    See also Ellis, David; Fulton, Cara; Tetaz, Eve.
  - Forschungsinstitut für Geistes- und Sozialwissenschaften (FIGS), See Universität Gesamthochschule Siegen.
  - Freeman-Garrott, Gloria, 1975-1976; 1982,; 1992; BC was on Freeman's dissertation committee; correspondence, resesarch notes, copies of dissertation and other papers; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Freie Universität Berlin, 1982 (Box 9)
    See also Doerry, Gerd; Lühr, Volker.
  - Freire, Paolo, notes, printed material; 2 folders (Box 9)
    See also Audiovisual material: Paolo Freire and also possibly Audiovisual material: [Side 1] Budget Comm Meeting 5/22/72 / Freire by Gittens / Johnson.
  - Friedenthal-Haase, Martha, 1981-1987; 1990,; 1991,; 1993; correspondence, MFH's articles, papers, clippings; 2 folders (Box 10)
    See also Audiovisual material: Martha Friedenthal-Haase.
  - Fuentes, Carlos, 1987-1988; clippings, brochure for lecture series (Box 10)
  - Fueyo [?], Al and Mary, 1993 (Box 10)
  - Fulbright
    - Application for 1975/1976 year, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Application for 1988/1989 year, 1986-1987 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1976; 1979; correspondence from Fulbright Commission, Council for Exchange of International Scholars, others (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986-1987; BC notes, receipts, souvenirs (Box 10)
  - Fulton, Cara, 1990-1994; former student, Peace Corps volunteer in Honduras; correspondence, newsletters, Fulton's writings (articles, papers) (Box 11)
  - Gayfer, Margaret, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Gikuhi, David, 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Gleazer, Edmund, 1987; undated; papers, articles (Box 11)
    See also USSR/Finland trip.
  - Glesne, Corrine, 1990; 1992; correspondence, syllabus for Glesne's class in participatory research (Box 11)
  - Goddard College, 1966-1971; 1981,; 1982,; 1987,; 1991-1993,; 1995 (Box 11)
  - Gove, Barbara, 1982; undated (Box 11)
  - Governor's State University (University Park, Illinois), 1978 (Box 11)
  - Griffith, William S., 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - Gulf Publishing Company, undated (Box 11)
  - Happ, Eva, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Harney, Klaus, 1988-1989; correspondence, photocopy of book chapter co-written by Harney (Box 11)
  - Harris, Barbara, 1980; 1982 (Box 11)
  - Hart, Marja and Peter, See Orivesi, Finland workshop.
  - Hattie M. Strong Foundation (Washington, DC), 1971; 1975-1977 (Box 11)
  - Hiemstra, Roger, See Syracuse University Kellogg Project.
  - Higher Education Resource Services, 1973-1974; 1977 (Box 11)
  - Highlander Folk School (Monteagle, Tennessee), See Highlander Research and Education Center.
  - Highlander Research and Education Center (New Market, Tennessee), 1984; 1987-1989,; 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    See also Horton, Myles; Research material: Folk schools.
  - Hinzen, Heribert, 1996 (Box 11)
  - Hochman, Joe, 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Holden, Mrs. Russell, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Hopper, Dorothy, 1992; 1997 (Box 11)
  - Horn, Jakob, 1996-1997 (Box 11)
  - Horton, Myles, undated; manuscript of paper, "A survey of residential adult schools in the United States and Canada" (Box 11)
  - Hudspeth, Susan, 1988; 1992; correspondence, clippings, printed material on The Foxfire Fund, Branch School (Box 11)
  - Hughes, Langston, undated; clipping (Box 11)
  - Imel, Susan, 1990; correspondence, draft of BC's review of Landmarks in International Adult Education (Alexander Charters) (Box 11)
  - International Associates in Adult Education, 1988-1996; IAAE was a joint venture of CAEO and ICAE; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - International Associates in Adult Education, undated; IAAE was a joint venture of CAEO and ICAE (Box 12)
  - International Conference on Adult Education (5th), 1997 (Box 12)
  - International Congress of University Adult Educators (ICUAE), 1985-1988 (Box 12)
  - International Council for Adult Education (ICAE)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1993 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1996; undated (Box 13)
    - annual meeting (Trinidad and Tobago), 1981 (Box 13)
    - annual meeting (Buenos Aires), 1985 (Box 13)
    - annual meeting (Sri Lanka), 1986 (Box 13)
    - annual meeting (Harare, Zimbabwe), 1989 (Box 13)
    - annual meeting (Bangkok), 1990; 2 folders (Box 13)
      See also Bangkok/Hong Kong trip; World Conference on Education for All; Personal papers: Journals: 1990 [Hong Kong/Bangkok trip]
    - annual meeting (Gothenburg, Sweden), 1991 (Box 14)
    - annual meeting (Rio de Janeiro), 1992 (Box 14)
    - annual meeting (Aranjuez, Spain), 1993; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - annual meeting (Aranjuez, Spain), 1993 (Box 15)
    - annual meeting (Cairo), 1994; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Annual meeting reports (by BC), 1990-1994 (Box 15)
    - Awards, 1991; undated; material on the J. Roby Kidd, Dame Nita Barrow, and Nabila Breir awards (Box 15)
    - Criminal justice programme, 1987-1992; correspondence, programme newsletters, papers by Bill Cosman (Box 15)
    - Environmental education, 1992; undated (Box 15)
    - Health and popular education, 1987-1989 (Box 15)
    - Women's program, 1985-1986; 1989-1991,; undated; correspondence, clippings, program newsletters, BC notes (Box 16)
    - Printed material
      - Directories and membership lists, 1986-1994 (Box 16)
      - ICAE newsletter, 1986-1994 (Box 16)
      - Miscellaneous, undated; bibliographies, publication announcements, fliers (Box 16)
    - Reports, miscellaneous, undated; includes paper by Francesco Vio Grossi (ICAE president) (Box 16)
  - International Development Conference (Washington, DC), 1985; 1987 (Box 17)
  - International Journal of Adult Education, 1969-1970 (Box 17)
  - International League for Social Commitment in Adult Education (ILSCAE), 1986-1988 (Box 17)
  - International Literacy Year, See International Task Force on Literacy (ITFL).
  - International Self-Directed Learning Symposium (7th), 1992 (Box 17)
  - International Society for Comparative Adult Education (ISCAE), 1988-1993; correspondence, memos, a number of brief biographies of ISCAE members (Box 17)
  - International Symposium on Adult Education (Shenyang, China), 1993 (Box 17)
  - International Task Force on Literacy (ITFL), 1988-1994; correspondence, clippings, paper by BC, paper by Makoto Yamaguchi, newsletters (Box 17)
  - Jarvis, Peter, 1985; undated (Box 17)
    See also Adult Education Through World Collaboration.
  - Job search, 1969-1970; correspondence with various institutions regarding potential openings for BC in the Maryland/Virginia area, after her husband accepted a position at George Mason; arranged alphabetically by institution (Box 17)
  - Johann Wolfgang Goethe-Universität, See Happ, Eva; Harney, Klaus; Wersich, Rüdiger.
  - Johannes Gutenberg-Universität Mainz, 1976 (Box 17)
  - John F. Kennedy Schule, 1975 (Box 17)
  - Jones-Wilson, Faustine, 1977; 1978,; 1981,; 1991,; 1993-1996; correspondence, many clippings regarding University of the District of Columbia's financial troubles in 1995-1996 (Box 17)
    See also Journal of Negro Education; "Not Just Kid Stuff".
  - Jordan, Bob and Kathy, 1983; 1988,; 1990,; 1991,; 1992,; 1994 (Box 17)
  - Jossey-Bass Inc., 1980; 1992,; undated (Box 17)
  - Journal of Negro Education, 1986 (Box 17)
  - Juliana, Queen of the Netherlands, 1964 (Box 17)
  - Kahuthu, Jane W., See Kimathi Institute of Technology.
  - Karani, Florida, 1985-1987; undated (Box 17)
    See also Writings: Papers: The emerging role of women adult educators in Kenya.
  - Kariuki, Mary, See Chesaro, Lina Tungo.
  - Kellog Foundation, 1975; 1990-1991,; undated (Box 17)
    See also Adult Education Through World Collaboration; Syracuse University Kellogg Project.
  - Kent, Roberta, 1974; literary agent; correspondence regarding proposed book American Men: Their Changing Roles (Box 18)
  - Kenya trips
    - Correspondence, 1981; 1982,; 1985,; undated (Box 18)
      See also Reche, George; Kimathi Institute of Technology.
    - Photographs, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Slides, 1981; 1 carousel and 3 small boxes (Oversize 5)
    - Trip report, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Miscellany, receipts, souvenirs (Box 18)
      See also Personal papers: Journals: 1981 [Kenya trip]; Personal papers: Journals: 1985 [Kenya trip].
  - Kimathi Institute of Technology, 1985; undated (Box 18)
  - Kinyanjui, Peter, 1981; 1987,; undated; correspondence, two papers by Kinyanjui (Box 18)
  - Knowles, Malcolm
    - Audiorecording, Malcolm Knowles and Cyril Houle, See Audiovisual material: Knowles - Houle #2.
    - Audiorecording, Malcolm Knowles and Leonard Freedman, See Audiovisual material: Malcolm Knowles, Leonard Freedman.
    - Correspondence, 1965-1970; 1973-1975,; 1980,; 1988,; 1990-1992,; 1994,; 1997 (Box 18)
  - Knox, Alan, 1992-1993; correspondence, draft of Knox's paper, "Global Perspectives on Strengthening Educational Programs for Less Advantaged Adults" (1993) (Box 18)
  - Kreuzer, Helmut and Ingrid, 1991; 1992 (Box 18)
  - Krieger Publishing, See Adult Education Through World Collaboration.
  - Kruh, Robert and Jan, 1982; 1994 (Box 18)
  - Langner, William, 1993 (Box 18)
  - Laubach Literacy, 1991 (Box 18)
  - Laurentian University, 1993; invitation to BC to be keynote speaker at conference (Box 18)
  - Lett-Simons, Barbara, 1988; tribute, in All-Stars Talent Show program (Box 18)
  - Life Pathways Inc., See Tetaz, Eve.
  - Lifelong Learning Research Conference (University of Maryland), 1987; proceedings (Box 18)
  - Lilia, 1991-1993; Russian pen friend from Arkhangelsk (Box 18)
  - Loring, Rosalind, 1968; 1974 (Box 18)
  - Lorton Prison College Program, 1978; 1981,; 1983,; 1990 (Box 19)
    BC gave several workshops for teachers at the Lorton Prison College Program. Material includes Lorton commencement programs, workshop outlines, student evaluations, handouts and supporting material
  - "Love and the Affluent Suburban Woman" (BC book chapter), 1974 (Box 19)
    See also Writings: Books: Love and the affluent American housewife/mother.
  - Lühr, Volker, 1974-1976; 1984-1987,; 1989,; undated (Box 19)
    See also Audiovisual material: German adult educators interviews: Lühr.
  - Luke, Robert A., undated; clipping of tributes (Box 19)
  - Marable, Manning
    - Audiorecordings, See Audiovisual material: Manning Marable (2 items).
    - Clippings, 1992 (Box 19)
  - März, Roswitha, 1996; correspondence, clippings (Box 19)
  - Masinde, Richard Wafula, 1985-1986 (Box 19)
  - Materials and Methods in Adult Education, 1976; 1987,; 1992 (Box 19)
  - Mazrui, Salma and Khalfan
    - Audiorecording, See Audiovisual material: Khalfan Mazrui.
    - Correspondence, 1985; 1987 (Box 19)
  - McCall Corporation, 1968; correspondence regarding "Womanpower in Action" forum (Box 19)
  - Mead, Margaret, 1962; 1977 (Box 19)
  - Metropolitan Washington Association of Adult and Continuing Education (MWAACE), 1984; 1986; correspondence, includes several photos from "Capital to Capital," a visit by German adult educators to the United States (Box 19)
  - Meulen, Saskia van der, 1969-1970; 1987,; 1990; See also Audiovisual material: Saskia (Moscow). (Box 19)
  - Mitchell, George J. (U.S. Senator), 1991 (Box 19)
  - Montana Housing Project, 1975 (Box 19)
    See also Writings: Papers: The story of the Montana Housing Project Educational Center.
  - Moore, David, 1984 (Box 19)
  - Morgan, Charlotte, 1984; 1987,; 1989,; undated; correspondence, writings (Box 19)
    See also "Falkenstein conference"; Adult Education in a Multicultural Society; Writings: Books: Adult Education in a Multicultural Society, chapter 4 material.
  - Muungano Women's Group, 1985-1986 (Box 19)
  - National Broadcasting Company (NBC), See WRC-TV.
  - National Council of Women in Sweden, 1970 (Box 19)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Higher Education Panel, 1983; BC was on the assessment team for the Higher Education Panel (Box 19)
  - Neal, Annie W., 1975-1976; Neal was assistant Dean at Federal City College (Box 19)
  - Niemi, John, 1977; 1980,; 1988,; 1992-1994; correspondence, article on education in Finland, adult education program in Finland, Russia and Estonia (1994) (Box 19)
  - North American Alliance for Popular and Adult Education, 1992-1994; undated; correspondence, notes, photographs (Box 19)
  - North American Consortium for International Adult Education, 1989-1990; undated; BC participated as representative of ICAE (Box 19)
  - Northern Illinois University, 1977; 1985-1986,; 1990,; 1992-1993; correspondence, printed material from RE:ACE (Box 19)
  - Northern Virginia Community College
    - Awards and recognitions, 1972 (Oversize 3)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1973; correspondence; syllabus and BC notes for the classes and workshops she taught (Box 20)
  - "Not Just Kid Stuff", undated; slide and tape presentation, with Faustine Jones-Wilson
    - Audio portion of presentation, See Audiovisual material: Not Just Kid Stuff.
    - Slides and script (Oversize 5)
  - Oels, Monika, 1983-1985; 1992 (Box 20)
    See also Audiovisual material: German adult educators interviews: Oels.
  - Oglala Lakota College, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Ogombe, Nelson, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Ohliger, John, 1994 (Box 20)
  - Oliver, Leonard P., 1994 (Box 20)
  - Operation Rescue, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Orivesi, Finland workshop, 1969-1970 (Box 20)
  - Osterling, Caroline, 1988; 1991 (Box 20)
  - Pädagogische Hochschule Berlin, 1974 (Box 20)
    See also Engels, Elmar; Lühr, Volker.
  - Paige, Joseph C., 1973 (Box 20)
    See also University of the District of Columbia: Correspondence (1971-1972) and University of the District of Columbia: Clippings (1973)
  - Payton, Phillip W., 1992; correspondence, paper by Payton, "Multicultural perspectives for an adult-oriented curriculum" (1992) (Box 20)
  - Peace Corps, 1991; undated (Box 20)
  - Peters, John, undated; manuscript of paper, "Case of the Bowmaker" (Box 20)
  - Peters, Marianne, 1978; 1986-1987; correspondence, resume, report by Ernest Cassara on Peters' proposed project (Box 20)
  - Phillips, Gene, 1969; 1973,; 1977,; 1978,; 1991 (Box 20)
  - Philosphy of adult education inventory, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Pitkin, Royce, 1993 (Box 20)
  - Pope, Elizabeth, 1969; 1975,; undated (Box 20)
  - Postmaster, 1985; 1987,; 1990,; 1991,; 1994 (Box 20)
  - "Professors of Adult Education Survey on Racism and Diversity", 1992; correspondence, completed questionnaires, notes; 2 folders (Box 20)
    Paper resulting from this study is located in Writings: Papers: Diversity by any other name.
  - Pross, Helge, 1979-1984; undated; correspondence, clippings, obituary, photocopy of Pross' book Die erste repräsentatitive Untersuchung über nichterwerbstätige Ehefrauen; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Prosser, Roy, undated (Box 21)
  - Randolph-Macon Women's College, 1977 (Box 21)
  - Rathman, Mahadev, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Reche, George, 1985-1987; correspondence, dissertation; 2 folders (Box 21)
    See also Karani, Florida; Lorton Prison College Program; Writings: Papers: Traditional adult education in Kenya.
  - Reeves, Joan, 1986; undated (Box 21)
    See also Writings: Books: Adult Education in a Multicultural Society: Introduction and chapters (Chapter 10).
  - Reischmann, Jost, 1990; undated (Box 21)
  - Rethinking Adult Education for Development, 1991-1993 (Box 21)
    See also Writings: Book chapters: Rethinking Adult Education for Development.
  - Richard, Jerry and Carolyn, 1997 (Box 21)
  - Rockland High School
    - Awards and recognitions, 1994 (Oversize 3)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 21)
  - Ross-Gordon, Jovita, 1991 (Box 21)
  - Sadjah, O.G. Philippe, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Sauer, —, 1961; literary agent, concerning a children's book BC wrote (Box 21)
  - Sausen, Helmut, undated; manuscript of paper, "Amerikanische Bildungspolitik, Dargestellt am Beispiel der Beruflichen Weiterbildung" (Box 21)
    See also Audiovisual material: German adult educators interviews: Sausen.
  - Scholarship options, 1965; correspondence with various individuals and organizations regarding BC's search for funding to return to school (Box 21)
  - Schöpp-Schilling, Hanna-Beate, See Aspen Insitute Berlin.
  - Semmler, Renate, See Amerika Haus.
  - Senate pages, 1970; letters and clippings concerning the barring of women from being Senate Pages (Box 21)
  - SeniorSERVE, 1996-1997 (Box 21)
  - Siegen lecture trip, 1980-1982; undated; 2 folders (Box 21)
    See also Pross, Helge. For BC's lectures given during this trip, see Writings: Siegen lecture series.
  - Siegle, Peter, 1967; 1969-1970,; 1980,; 1985 (Box 22)
    See also Writings: School papers: Social foundations of education.
  - Snowe, Olympia (U.S. Representative), 1986; 1991 (Box 22)
  - Society for Participatory Research in Asia, 1982; 1987-1991,; 1993; correspondence, newsletters, two books, paper by Rajesh Tandon, "Politics of Life: Knowledge, Science and Education in the Contemporary World," publication "Participatory Evaluation: Issues and Concerns"; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Sork, Thomas J., 1978; 1992 (Box 22)
  - Sparr, Thea von, 1976 (Box 22)
  - Steichen, Edward, 1945; 1947,; 1964,; 1966,; 1971,; 1978,; 1979,; 1984,; 1988,; undated (Box 22)
    BC was Steichen's secretary at the Navy Department and assisted in the preparation of two of his books. Included here are correspondence, letter of recommendation, clippings, and photographs and printed material from "Power in the Pacific" exhibit. Two of Steichen's books, signed and inscribed by Steichen to "BB" (Beverly Benner) have been removed from the colletion for separate cataloging.
  - Stiefel, Elisabeth, 1981-1983; 1988,; 1996,; 1997,; undated; correspondence, article in German with translation by BC (Box 22)
  - Syracuse University Kellogg Project, 1991; correspondence, technical report "English Language Adult Education Books: Their Value to Adult Educators" (Box 22)
  - Tandon, Rajesh, See Society for Participatory Research in Asia.
  - Technische Universität Berlin, 1978; undated; letter, photocopy of paper (?) by TUB professor Klaus Döring, "Zur Didaktik des Lernens mit Erwachsenen" (Box 22)
  - Tetaz, Eve, 1988-1998 (Box 22)
    Tetaz was a former student of BC's who worked with her on the Montana Housing Project. Included here are correspondence, clippings, report "Single Parenting: Views of Women in Jubilee Housing," and much printed material from Tetaz's organization, Life Pathways Inc., which was modelled on the Montana project
  - Thorne, Shirley L., 1988-1998; "college roomate [sic] and lifelong friend for whom my daughter is named"; several papers by Thorne on experiences of immigrant women (Box 22)
  - Tough, Allen, 1977; manuscript of paper "Major learning efforts: Recent research and future directions" (Box 22)
  - Tufts University, 1963; 1965 (Box 22)
  - TVT Associates, 1990 (Box 22)
  - UNESCO Institute for Education, 1974-1976 (Box 22)
  - Unitarian Universalist Association, 1961; 1962,; 1964,; 1966-1967,; 1970,; 1991,; 1993,; undated; includes the Unitarian Universalist Women's Federation; correspondence, printed material, sermon on "Margaret Sanger and What Women Can Do for Peace" (Box 22)
    See also Writings: Miscellaneous: Unitarian Universalist Church.
  - United Nations Conference on Environment and Development (Rio de Janeiro)
    - BC notes, program, 1992 (Box 23)
    - Papers, 1992; includes BC's paper (Box 23)
    - Printed material, clippings, 1992; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Printed material, clippings (oversize) (Oversize 1)
  - United Nations Decade for Women, Nairobi, 1985; correspondence, papers, conference material, conference report by BC, advance copy of final United Nations report; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - "United Nations Decade for Women Information Kit for NGO's", 1985 (Box 24)
    See also Memorabilia (oversize).
  - United States Department of Agriculture Graduate School
    - Awards and recognitions, 1990 (Oversize 3)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1989; 1990,; 1993 (Box 24)
  - United States Department of Commerce, 1981 (Box 24)
  - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
  - Universität Gesamthochschule Siegen, 1981-1985; 1990,; 1995-1996 (Box 24)
    See also Pross, Helge; Writings: Miscellaneous: FIGS speech.
  - Universität Regensburg, 1982; from Ernest Cassara (Box 24)
  - Universität Tübingen, 1984; correspondence, notes, clippings, receipts, paper by BC, "Observations on the status of adult education in Germany today" delivered at the university (Box 24)
    See also Dohmen, Gunther; Reischmann, Jost.
  - University of the District of Columbia
    The University of the District of Columbia (UDC) was created out of three other universities, one of which was Federal City College (FCC) where BC taught for several years. This subseries contains material for both FCC and UDC.
    See also Harris, Barbara; Jones-Wilson, Faustine; Neal, Annie W.; Paige, Joseph C.; Rathman, Mahadev.
    - Awards and recognitions, 1981-1986; 1988-1990 (Oversize 3)
    - Clippings, 1968-1969; 1973-1977; 1980,; 1982-1984,; 1993; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Commencement programs, 1973-1984; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Commencement programs, 1988-1989 (Box 25)
    - Conference on International Adult Education, 5th Annual, 1985; 1991 (Box 25)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1991; 1997; undated; 4 folders (Box 25)
    - Course catalogs, 1971-1973; 1976-1977,; 1979-1980,; 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Course lists, syllabi, 1970; 1986-1990 (Box 26)
    - Discrimination case, 1971 (Box 26)
    - Faculty evaluations (Box 26)
    - Faculty evaluations (Box 27)
    - Grade book, 1988-1989 (Box 27)
    - Personnel actions, 1971; 1974,; 1976,; 1982,; 1986,; 1988 (Box 27)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 27)
    - President's inauguration programs, 1975; 1982,; 1983,; 1988 (Box 27)
    - Student lists, 1988-1990; undated (Box 27)